megaporn24.com 2010-05-22

# Privacy Policy

This policy explains the privacy practices for Glamourcam video community. In order to provide interactive computer billing and fraud services, Glamourcam video community collects and uses certain information about you. This policy explains what we collect, what we use and how you can interact with Glamourcam video community in order to ensure the accuracy of the data we collect and use.

**Information Collection:**  
Visitors can access our Web site home page and browse our Web site without disclosing any personal data. However, in order to provide you with a particular product or service online, Glamourcam video community may request that you voluntarily supply Glamourcam video community with primary personal data (such as name and email address) and identifiers (such as credit card number and web site password). Glamourcam video community gives you the option of using a secure transmission method of sending such information.  
Glamourcam video community receives and stores all information that you enter in our Web site and billing pages. In addition, Glamourcam video community collects information about you during your visit, such as your IP Address, and Glamourcam video community employs its software in order to ascertain your physical location when making a purchase. However, we do not collect information from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. You are required to provide Glamourcam video community with accurate and up-to-date information, and failure to provide Glamourcam video community with such information could result in voiding your Agreement with Glamourcam video community.

**Information Use:**  
Glamourcam video community is the sole owner of the information collected on its sites. Glamourcam video community will not sell, share, or rent this information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed it this policy. Glamourcam video community shall release data when required by law, to enforce its Agreement, or the contract rights of its clients. Glamourcam video community shares the following data with the owner/operator of the web site from which you are purchasing goods and services utilizing Glamourcam video community services: the URL you are purchasing goods or services from, your e-mail address, your name, your address, your phone number, your date of birth, and your agreement to be bound by Glamourcam video community terms and conditions. Glamourcam video community uses the data it collects for the technical administration of the Web site, research and development, and fraud deterrence.

**Information sharing:**  
We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.

**Email correspondence:**  
Glamourcam video community may request a confirmation when you receive and open and e-mail communication delivered by Glamourcam video community. We archive and identify the origination IP address of all email sent into our network.

**Third party information:**  
Occasionally, Glamourcam video community receives information from third parties to compare it to information that you had provided to Glamourcam video community for fraud prevention purposes.

**Cookies:**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the visitor's hard drive containing information about the visitor. Glamourcam video community employs "cookie" technology. We use the Cookie to store personal date, to authenticate you as a Site user, for security purposes, and to track our affiliate click-throughs and sign-up rate.

**Children:**  
Glamourcam video community does not request, or knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 18. Glamourcam video community takes specific steps to protect the privacy of children by making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child's personal data Additionally, to ensure that children's privacy is respected on our Web site, Glamourcam video community requires age verification on every inquiry. Furthermore, Glamourcam video community does not give children the ability to post messages or otherwise distribute information about themselves on our web site.

**Security:**  
We date every protection to protect our visitors' information. We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access; improper use or disclosure; unauthorized modification; unlawful destruction or accidental loss. Glamourcam video community utilizes Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software when receiving and transmitting electronic payments. Glamourcam video community encrypts the information that you provided.  
In addition, Glamourcam video community does everything to protect your information off-line. All employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. Glamourcam video community conducts background and credit checks on all of its employees prior to employment. Glamourcam video community employs a username and password scheme in order to limit and achieve access to our computer network by our employees and third parties.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information:**  
You may access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, updating, and in some instances deleting from our system any information deemed inaccurate. You may request to access your information by sending a request to: Administrator.
